<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software on cloud daydreams</title>
    <link>https://arrjay.github.io/categories/software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software on cloud daydreams</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>rbergero@gmail.com (RJ Bergeron)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>rbergero@gmail.com (RJ Bergeron)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 02:58:57 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://arrjay.github.io/categories/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Objectgraph Tag Hack</title>
      <link>https://arrjay.github.io/posts/objectgraph-tag-hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 02:58:57 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>rbergero@gmail.com (RJ Bergeron)</author>
      <guid>https://arrjay.github.io/posts/objectgraph-tag-hack/</guid>
      <description>Hacking in Facebook Object Graph Image tags for hugo posts Just detailing that as of this commit I added support for setting Facebook Object Graph preview-image settings in my Hugo templates. It was really to add in the front matter, actually, once I realized you can refer to anything in front matter under Params. The main tricky thing was FB wanted absolute URIs, so I had to use absURL (which I did, in the next commit).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment Variables Rule Everything Around You</title>
      <link>https://arrjay.github.io/posts/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 00:18:42 -0400</pubDate>
      <author>rbergero@gmail.com (RJ Bergeron)</author>
      <guid>https://arrjay.github.io/posts/environment/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s lots of discussion for operating systems about processes, ipc, files and such, I wanted to take a moment and touch on some internals I find incredibly useful in my day to day work. Environment variables!
NOTE: I&amp;rsquo;m really only covering Linux/OS X/POSIX class systems here, Windows (and PowerShell) have some slightly different edges.
What Via Wikipedia - an environment variable is &amp;ldquo;a dynamic-named value that can affect the way running processes will behave on a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I chose Hugo for setting up this blog</title>
      <link>https://arrjay.github.io/posts/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 14:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>rbergero@gmail.com (RJ Bergeron)</author>
      <guid>https://arrjay.github.io/posts/hugo/</guid>
      <description>So this site is set up using Hugo and I figure I&amp;rsquo;d detail a little bit of why.
Static generator with a live updater One of the easier ways to do hosting is to have a simple collection of files to upload to a webserver, rather than building a server environment to run a blog engine. This also gives you the capability to more easily move your site between providers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>